aiprx.com 2017-08-24

# PRIVACY POLICY

130262549 v2 ©2017 Ai Media Group, llc.                                                                                     1
                                                         PRIVACY POLICY
    At Ai Media Group, llc. (referred to as “Company,” “us” or “we”), we recognize that your customer’s privacy is
    important. This Policy discloses the Company’s privacy practices, in connection with all products and services
    we may offer to you (collectively referred to as the “Services”). This Policy also covers how personal and other
    information that we receive or collect about your customers is treated. Please read the information below to learn
    the following regarding your use of our Services.
    We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes
    in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your
    account, and/or by placing a prominent notice on our web site. Your continued use of our Services after such
    modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) your agreement to abide
    and be bound by that Policy.
    If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us at: privacy@aimediagroup.com.
    1. Types of Information We Collect
        In order to provide you with the Services, we collect two types of information about your customers: Personally
        Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Aggregate Information.
        Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who your
        customers are. When your customers engage in certain activities, such as clicking on an advertisement or
        calling a phone number on the site, etc. we may collect PII about your customers.
        Examples of PII may include your customers’ first and last name and or company name, email address,
        mailing address (including zip code), employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers and
        other identifying information.
        Aggregate Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We
        gather certain information about your customers when they click on advertisements. This information, which
        is collected in a variety of different ways, is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated
        basis. This information may include the Website’s Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that points to the site your
        customer just came from, which URL your customer goes to after clicking on an advertisement, what browser
        your customer is using, and your customer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.
    2. How We Collect and Use Information
        We do not collect any PII about your customer unless they click on an advertisement created through the use
        of our Services.
        We will primarily use your customer’s PII to track the amount of times your advertisement is accessed or
        to track the activity of your customer in connection with their viewing of an advertisement. We will also use
        certain forms of PII to improve your marketing and promotional efforts or to statistically analyze usage. We
        may use PII to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. Finally, we may
        use your PII to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our
        Service contract and this Privacy Policy.
                                      1359 Broadway 5th Floor, New York, NY 10018 • Tel 212 660 2400 • www.aimediagroup.com

130262549 v2 ©2017Ai Media Group, llc.                                                                                     2
       We may also collect certain Aggregate Information. For example, we may use your customer’s IP address
       to diagnose problems with servers or software and to gather demographic information. Our third party
       advertising partners may also provide us with aggregate, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many
       ads were presented and clicked upon.
    3. Cookies
       We may store cookies on your customers’ computer in order to collect certain aggregate data about your
       customers. A cookie is a small data text file which is stored on your customers’ computer that uniquely
       identifies your customers’ browser. Cookies may also include more personalized information, such as your
       customer’s IP address, browser type, the server your customer’s computer is logged onto, and the area code
       and zip code associated with your customer’s computer. We may use cookies to perform tasks such as:
       monitoring aggregate site usage metrics, storing account and advertising preferences that have been set, and
       personalizing the Services we make available to your customer.
    4. Release of Information
       We will not sell, trade, or rent your customer’s PII to others. We do provide some of our product and service
       offerings through contractual arrangements made with affiliates, service providers, partners and other third
       parties (“Service Partners”). We and our Service Partners may need to use some PII in order to perform tasks
       between our respective sites, or to deliver products or services to you.
       We will encourage our Service Partners to adopt and promote strong privacy policies. However, the use of your
       customers’ PII by our Service Partners is governed the respective privacy policies of those providers, and is not
       subject to our control. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the
       use and disclosure of information we collect from your customer. Our Advertising and Service Partners, have
       their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. We are not responsible for the
       policies or practices of third parties.
       Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide PII to the appropriate
       governmental authorities. In such cases, we will disclose PII upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or
       to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in
       identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement
       agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
       We may also provide Aggregate Information about our customers’ sales, traffic patterns, and related information
       to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.
    5. Security of Your PII
       You can be assured that your customers’ PII is secure, consistent with current industry standards. We strive
       to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration,
       disclosure or destruction of PII. For example:
       •    We also only keep collected information and use it only for the purposes for which it was collected or to
            comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.
       •    We limit access to PII only to specific employees, contractors and agents who have a reasonable need to
            come into contact with your information. For example, we may provide members of our technical support
            team with limited access to your account in order to allow them to troubleshoot.
       •    Additionally, we also employ a number of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect PII. Our
            secure servers and our data centers are protected by industry-standard encryption, and our servers reside
            behind firewalls and employ high-level password protection.
                                     1359 Broadway 5th Floor, New York, NY 10018 • Tel 212 660 2400 • www.aimediagroup.com

130262549 v2 ©2017Ai Media Group, llc.                                                                                     3
       Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100%
       secure. As a result, while we strive to protect PII, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy
       limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) the security, integrity and privacy of
       any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
    6. Miscellaneous
       Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose PII about minors.
       If you have any questions, concerns or inquiries about our Privacy Policy, or our use of PII, or our privacy
       practices, please contact us at: privacy@aimediagroup.com. You can also reach our Privacy Compliance
       Officer by sending written correspondence to:
       Ai Media Group
       1359 Broadway, 5th Floor
       New York, NY 10018
       Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer
    PROVISIONS SPECIFIC TO EUROPEAN INDIVIDUALS
    Who is the data controller?
       For the purpose of any legislation or binding local regulations implementing the provisions of Directive 95/46/
       EC of the European Parliament (the “EU Directive”), the data controller of your EEA-based customers’ Personal
       Data (as defined below) is typically you. However, in the event that the EU Directive classifies the Company as
       data controller in respect of your EEA-based customers’ Personal Data the remaining provisions of this Policy
       shall apply.
       Please note that even if the Company is not the data controller of your EEA-based customers’ Personal Data,
       we will still take reasonable endeavours to ensure that we treat such Personal Data in accordance with both
       this Policy and our obligations as a data processor of such Personal Data under the EU Directive.
    What constitutes Personal Data?
       “Personal Data” extends the definition of “PII” (as outlined above), to include any information by which an
       individual can actually be identified or could be identifiable, whether simply from that information alone, or
       in combination with any other information which is in our control, and includes “personal data” as defined in
       the EU Directive. Each reference to PII in this Policy shall, for your customers who are based in the European
       Economic Area (the “EEA”), be read as a reference to Personal Data.
    Customer’s acceptance of our Policy
       Your customers whose Personal Data and Aggregate information we collect are required to give their consent
       before we start to collect such information from them by acknowledging the notification. In addition, your
       customers may opt-out of such collection at any time by using their browser to block their cookies.
    Our policy towards children
       In accordance with applicable European Union guidance on the practice, we do not collect or process any
       Personal Data to target adverts to children. Accordingly, we do not create consumer segments that specifically
       target children under 13 years old.
                                     1359 Broadway 5th Floor, New York, NY 10018 • Tel 212 660 2400 • www.aimediagroup.com

130262549 v2 ©2017Ai Media Group, llc.                                                                                     4
    We store and process Personal Data outside the EEA.
       Personal Data and Aggregate Information that we collect from your customers will be transferred to, and
       stored at, a destination outside the EEA. It will also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work
       for us or for one of our suppliers.
       You and your customers should be aware that the data protection and privacy regulations that apply in
       countries outside the EEA may not offer the same level of protection as provided for inside the EEA.
       We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your EEA-based customers’ Personal Data, wherever
       it is held or processed, is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy and the EU Directive.
    Access to information.
       The EU Directive gives your customers the right to access certain information we hold about them. If any
       individual to whom the EU Directive applies wishes to request access to the information we hold about them
       in accordance with the EU Directive, this access request may be subject to a fee of US $10 to meet our
       reasonable costs in providing them with details of the information we hold. If wish to make such a request,
       please contact privacy@aimediagroup.com.
                                     1359 Broadway 5th Floor, New York, NY 10018 • Tel 212 660 2400 • www.aimediagroup.com
